[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "Do you confirm to be comfortable working in an environment with tight deadlines and frequent changes?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "Do you confirm to handle unexpected challenges and uncertainties in your work?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Strongly Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "When faced with conflicting priorities, do you confirm to be able to prioritize and manage your tasks?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "In a team setting, do you confirm that it is important for you to maintain a calm and stable work environment?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Strongly Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "Do you confirm to be able to adapt to changes in work processes or procedures?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "When given repetitive tasks, do you confirm to maintain your motivation and focus?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "Do you confirm to be patient when you are dealing with unexpected delays or disruptions in your work?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Strongly Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "Do you confirm that you are comfortable with routine and predictability in your daily work tasks?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "Do you prefer a consistent and stable work routine? Rate your answer and provide reason",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "Do you confirm that it is important for you to establish and maintain long-term relationships with your colleagues?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Strongly Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "When facing tight deadlines, do you confirm to manage your stress and pressure?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "Do you confirm to adapt well to changes in the organizational structure or team dynamics?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "Do you confirm that you are comfortable with routine and repetitive tasks? Rate your answer and provide reason if you feel otherwise",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Neutral"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "Do you confirm to handle situations well where there is a lack of clear instructions or guidance? Rate your answer and explain how.",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "When faced with conflicting opinions within a team, do you confirm to contribute to resolving the conflicts?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Strongly Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "Do you confirm to approach situations with patience where you need to wait for information or decisions from others? Rate your answer and explain properly.",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "In a team setting, do you ensure that everyone is heard and their opinions are considered? Rate your answer and explain how.",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Strongly Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "Do you confirm that it is important for you to establish a consistent work routine and schedule?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "When facing unexpected changes, do you confirm to communicate and reassure your team members?",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Strongly Agree"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "Do you confirm to handle situations where there is ambiguity or lack of clarity in your tasks? Rate your answer and explain how.",
        "options": [
            "Strongly Disagree",
            "Disagree",
            "Neutral",
            "Agree",
            "Strongly Agree"
        ],
        "answer": "Agree"
    }
]